<resources>
    <string name="app_name">helping</string>
    <string name="app_welcome">Welcome To MyApp</string>
    <string name="scroll">Accounting is the system of recording financial transactions with both numbers
        and text in the form of financial statements. It provides an essential tool for billing customers,
        keeping track of assets and liabilities (debts), determining profitability, and tracking the flow
        of cash. The system is largely self-regulated and designed for the users of financial information,
        who are referred to as stakeholders: business owners, lenders, employees, managers, customers, and
        others.
        Stakeholders utilize financial statements to help make business, lending, and investment decisions.
    Accounting has several specialized fields and roles. Private (internal) accounting generally refers
        to accountants who work within a single business entity. Small business accountants may assume
        general roles which require preparing the records (bookkeeping) and performing bank reconciliations.
        Accounting professionals are generally divided into three fields: tax, audit, and advisory. The tax
        field focuses on federal, state, and local tax filings. Audit roles test the validity of financial
        statements and internal controls. Advisory services perform general financial consulting.
        Public accounting firms have several different clients,
        whereas private accounting refers to working for one specific business entity.accounting standards set
        guidelines and rules for financial statement preparation. These are set via a combination of private
        industry organizations in cooperation with government committees. Generally Accepted Accounting Practices
        in the United States (US GAAP) largely governs the rules for recording transactions and disclosing
        critical business information to stakeholders. International Financial Reporting Standards (IFRS)
        governs international standards. Both systems require the use of double entry accounting.
        While both sets of standards are similar, there are significant differences such as allowed
        inventory methodologies and reporting asset valuation.</string>
    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
</resources>